top of page

Log In

NOTICE: Our Terms of Service has recently been updated. View Terms [here.](https://www.blazeapp.net/terms-of-service)

Privacy Policy
==============

Welcome to our Privacy Policy!

​

Your privacy and security are paramount to us at Blaze. We strive to be transparent and honest about how we handle your data. This Privacy Policy outlines our practices regarding the collection, use, and protection of your personal information.

​

1\. Consent for Minors:

If you are under 13 years old, you must obtain permission from your parents/guardians before using Blaze. We adhere to regulations such as COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act) to ensure compliance and protect minors' privacy.

​

2\. Data Collection:

We collect the following information:

\- Username  
\- Email Address  
\- Location (for data reports and IP blocking purposes)  
   
3\. Use Of Information:

We prioritize your privacy and only use your data for the following purposes:

\- Contacting you  
\- Data reports for public display (non-identifiable data) to improve our services and report our website's progress.  
\- Blocking IPs if necessary for security purposes.

​

4\. Data Protection:

We are committed to protecting your data. We do not engage in the sale or tracking of your personal information. However, please note that our website builder, WIX, may have its own data practices outlined in their Privacy Policy.

​

5\. User Controls:

Your control over your data is important to us. We aim to provide transparency and control to our users. Please feel free to contact us at [contactblaze@proton.me](mailto:contactblaze@proton.me) for privacy inquiries and complaints. We ensure timely responses within 60 days.

​

6\. Complaints and Enforcement:

If you believe that we have violated your rights or relevant privacy laws, you have the right to file a complaint. Please contact us at [contactblaze@proton.me](mailto:contactblaze@proton.me). For Californian residents, you may also file a complaint with the California Attorney General's office. For EU residents, you can file a complaint with relevant Data Protection Authorities.

​

7\. Changes to Policies:

We are committed to maintaining the highest standards of privacy protection. Any changes to our policies will be communicated to you promptly.

Last Updated: March 15, 2024  
Effective Date: March 18, 2024

The Flame of Social Media. Powered by WIX.

###### [Terms of Service](https://www.blazeapp.net/terms-of-service)

###### [Privacy Policy](https://www.blazeapp.net/privacy-policy)

bottom of page
